<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Sport Teams</string>
    <string name="category_list">Category List</string>
    <string name="team_list">Team List</string>
    <string name="team_detail">Team Detail</string>
    <string name="summary">SUMMARY</string>
    <string name="about">ABOUT THE TEAM</string>

    <string name="soccer">Soccer</string>
    <string name="basketball">Basketball</string>
    <string name="football">Football</string>

    <string name="founded">Founded</string>
    <string name="nickname">Nickname</string>
    <string name="stadium">Stadium</string>
    <string name="coach">Coach</string>

    <string name="real_madrid">Real Madrid C.F.</string>
    <string name="real_madrid_founded">1902</string>
    <string name="real_madrid_nickname">Los Blancos</string>
    <string name="real_madrid_stadium">Santiago Bernabéu Stadium</string>
    <string name="real_madrid_coach">Xabi Alonso</string>
    <string name="real_madrid_about">Based in Madrid, Spain, Real Madrid is one of the most successful football clubs in history. The team has a rich history of winning domestic and international titles, including a record number of UEFA Champions League trophies. The club\'s global fan base and "galácticos" policy of signing superstar players have made it a powerhouse on and off the field.</string>
    <string name="barcelona">F.C. Barcelona</string>
    <string name="barcelona_founded">1899</string>
    <string name="barcelona_nickname">Blaugrana</string>
    <string name="barcelona_stadium">Estadi Olímpic Lluís Companys</string>
    <string name="barcelona_coach">Hansi Flick</string>
    <string name="barcelona_about">F.C. Barcelona is a club with a deep connection to Catalan identity. Known for their intricate passing and attacking "tiki-taka" style of play, they have a fierce rivalry with Real Madrid. Their historic home, Camp Nou, is one of the largest stadiums in the world.</string>
    <string name="psg">Paris Saint-Germain F.C.</string>
    <string name="psg_founded">1970</string>
    <string name="psg_nickname">Les Parisiens</string>
    <string name="psg_stadium">Parc des Princes</string>
    <string name="psg_coach">Luis Enrique</string>
    <string name="psg_about">Founded through a merger of two clubs, PSG has become the dominant force in French football since being acquired by Qatar Sports Investments. The team is renowned for its star-studded roster and its ambition to win the Champions League.</string>
    <string name="gsw">Golden State Warriors</string>
    <string name="gsw_founded">1946</string>
    <string name="gsw_nickname">The Dubs</string>
    <string name="gsw_stadium">Chase Center</string>
    <string name="gsw_coach">Steve Kerr</string>
    <string name="gsw_about">The Golden State Warriors are a professional basketball team that competes in the Western Conference of the NBA. They rose to prominence in the mid-2010s, winning multiple championships with a revolutionary style of play centered on three-point shooting and dynamic ball movement. The team is known for its "Splash Brothers" duo and a legacy of success.</string>
    <string name="celtics">Boston Celtics</string>
    <string name="celtics_founded">1946</string>
    <string name="celtics_nickname">The C\'s</string>
    <string name="celtics_stadium">TD Garden</string>
    <string name="celtics_coach">Joe Mazzulla</string>
    <string name="celtics_about">The Boston Celtics are one of the most storied franchises in all of professional sports. They hold the record for the most NBA championships and are famous for their tradition of excellence, a long list of legendary players, and their intense rivalry with the Los Angeles Lakers.</string>
    <string name="bucks">Milwaukee Bucks</string>
    <string name="bucks_founded">1968</string>
    <string name="bucks_nickname">The Bucks</string>
    <string name="bucks_stadium">Fiserv Forum</string>
    <string name="bucks_coach">Doc Rivers</string>
    <string name="bucks_about">The Milwaukee Bucks are a professional basketball team that competes in the Eastern Conference. After winning a championship in 1971 with Kareem Abdul-Jabbar, the franchise returned to the top in 2021, led by their superstar Giannis Antetokounmpo.</string>
    <string name="chiefs">Kansas City Chiefs</string>
    <string name="chiefs_founded">1960</string>
    <string name="chiefs_nickname">The Chiefs</string>
    <string name="chiefs_stadium">Arrowhead Stadium</string>
    <string name="chiefs_coach">Andy Reid</string>
    <string name="chiefs_about">The Kansas City Chiefs are a professional American football team that plays in the AFC West division. The Chiefs have a passionate fan base and are known for their high-powered offense. They have become a dominant force in the league in recent years, winning multiple Super Bowl titles behind a talented roster led by their star quarterback.</string>
    <string name="packers">Green Bay Packers</string>
    <string name="packers_founded">1919</string>
    <string name="packers_nickname">The Pack</string>
    <string name="packers_stadium">Lambeau Field</string>
    <string name="packers_coach">Matt LaFleur</string>
    <string name="packers_about">The Green Bay Packers are a community-owned professional football team and one of the most historic franchises in the NFL. They are famous for their loyal fan base, "The Frozen Tundra" of Lambeau Field, and a long legacy of iconic quarterbacks.</string>
    <string name="buccaneers">Tampa Bay Buccaneers</string>
    <string name="buccaneers_founded">1976</string>
    <string name="buccaneers_nickname">The Bucs</string>
    <string name="buccaneers_stadium">Raymond James Stadium</string>
    <string name="buccaneers_coach">Todd Bowles</string>
    <string name="buccaneers_about">The Tampa Bay Buccaneers are an NFL team that competes in the NFC South. Known for their distinct color scheme and pirate-ship-themed stadium, the Buccaneers have experienced both periods of struggle and immense success, including two Super Bowl victories.</string>
</resources>